### **ANNA THAMMAKANE**

ANNA.THAMMAKANE@GMAIL.COM | 615.772.5712

#### **SUMMARY**

I currently work as a customs brokerage agent and lead a two-person team for the highest volume account for the BNA branch, which I mostly work on independently. Aside from customs and compliance, I also assist as an account manager to address or escalate customer issues and to gather customer data to pinpoint areas of potential growth for the client. I have additional experience in sales, data analysis, reporting, and project management, as well as experience in graphic design and illustration.

# VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

NASHVILLE INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR EMPOWERMENT 2018

#### **EDUCATION**

### MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science August 2017

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### CUSTOMS BROKERAGE AGENT • EXPEDITORS INTERNATIONAL • MARCH 2017 TO CURRENT

- Constantly working at building and maintaining strong relationships with the customer, the service providers, other EI branches, and with U.S. government organizations to guarantee compliance to regulations at all times
- Assist as an account manager to troubleshoot problems like reporting, PSM database, EDI, and assist with addressing additional needs
- Worked towards becoming one of the top 3 revenue accounts for the Brokerage department within a year of acquiring the account
- Regularly achieve over 98% in all categories on the monthly scorecard provided by the client
- Seek and review methods to enhance productivity, KPI's, process improvements, compliance, and customer satisfaction, while increasing the profit margin

### DATA ANALYST/UM SCHEDULING COORDINATOR • CENTURION OF TN • MARCH 2015 TO OCTOBER 2016

- Worked as the regional office IT Liaison and TN representative for corporate Telemedicine Champion team, assisted AA with basic HR functions, provided internal support for the Scheduling Dept, and for general IT issues
- Collected, analyzed, and prepared data from all contracted state correctional facilities and utilized vendors to produce COMPSTAT, Narrative, Vacancy, and Annual reports to provide for the TN Department of Correction
- Managed employee matrix, PCNs, and OLRFs for Finance Department to accurately track new employees, personnel changes, and vacancies for the 700+ employees on the contract
- Assisted in implementing new scheduling system to streamline the appointment request process from the site level to the regional office
- Worked independently to reorganize reporting structure and redesign reports for presentation to client

## PT PROPERTY MANAGER • FOTRESS STORAGE • JUNE 2010 TO JANUARY 2013

- Responsible for tending to tenants, maintaining the office, and managing customer accounts on the weekends at all locations
- Worked on attracting potential customers with promotional material to help attain monthly rental/tenant quota
- Developed advertising for moving specials and marketed products sold inoffice to current and potential clientele
- Created promotional prices for current tenants to upgrade to larger units, which helped increased tenant occupancy by 10% every quarter

## CSR II/E-MAIL REP • BORDERS GROUP, INC. • AUGUST 2007 TO MAY 2010

- Handled all incoming customer inquiries to nationwide call center with an emphasis on promoting the Borders Rewards membership program
- Assisted in training new hires on the floor